{"results":[{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,18000","2/3,6000"],"answer":"3","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":1083},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","2/3,15000"],"answer":"0.66","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":64},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,20000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"2","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":105},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,5000","3/2,15000"],"answer":"0.33","options":["3","2","1.5","0.66","0.5","0.33"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":97},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","1/1,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":147},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","1/1,15000"],"answer":"0.66","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":73},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,15000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"1.5","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":107},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,15000","3/2,15000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":121},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,15000","1/1,5000"],"answer":"3","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":99},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":87},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,15000","2/3,5000"],"answer":"3","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":126},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","2/3,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":196},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,15000","2/3,10000"],"answer":"1.5","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":575},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["2/3,10000","1/1,15000"],"answer":"0.66","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":530},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,6000","2/3,18000"],"answer":"0.33","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":158},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","1/1,20000"],"answer":"2","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":189},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["1/1,10000","3/2,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":158},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"isolatedRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Rect1","description":"The first rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"},{"typeName":"Rect2","description":"The second rectangle","specifyInVis":"no","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3/2,10000","2/3,10000"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"rectangles","dataset":"dummy","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":567},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["3"],"answer":"0.66","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.66","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":6937},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["4"],"answer":"0.5","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":4895},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["5"],"answer":"0.33","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":3177},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["6"],"answer":"0.33","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"2","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":5248},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["7"],"answer":"2","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"2","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":5294},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["8"],"answer":"0.33","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.5","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":7822},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["9"],"answer":"0.5","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.66","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":5275},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["10"],"answer":"0.5","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.5","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":5668},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["11"],"answer":"2","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"1.5","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":6143},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["12"],"answer":"0.66","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.66","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":5651},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["13"],"answer":"2","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"2","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":4350},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["14"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"1","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":3926},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["15"],"answer":"3","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"3","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":5544},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["16"],"answer":"0.33","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.33","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":6450},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["17"],"answer":"2","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.5","accuracy":0.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":4714},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["18"],"answer":"1","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"1","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":4632},{"type":"task","task":{"name":"treemapRectangle","question":"What is the ratio of the areas of rectangles A and B?","description":"","inputs":[{"typeName":"Image","description":"Which of the images to show","specifyInVis":"yes","showInVis":"yes"}],"answer":{"type":"Options(fixed)","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"],"correctness":"yes"}},"taskInstance":{"inputs":["19"],"answer":"0.66","options":["0.33","0.5","0.66","1","1.5","2","3"]},"response":"0.66","accuracy":1.0,"viewer":"imageStimulus","dataset":"trees","group":"0_rectangles,dummy,isolatedRectangle;imageStimulus,trees,treemapRectangle","time":6603}]}